Guide to the National Grange of the Patrons of Husbandry records, 1842-1994
National Grange of the Patrons of Husbandry records, 1842-1994
- Series VII. Transportation Consultant - Charles Bowling
  - Association of American Railroads, 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 31 (a-d))
    Correspondence, amendments, newsletter, pamphlet. Includes Walter J. Little, Association of American Railroads.
  - William J. Augello, Jr., 1959 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    Correspondence, petitions, note, memo, news clipping.
  - Automobile Manufacturers Association, Inc., 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    Correspondence, statement, report.
  - Automotive Safety Foundation, 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    Correspondence, memo, pamphlets. Includes John L. Marks, Automotive Safety Foundation.
  - Frank L. Barton, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    Correspondence, statement. Includes United States Senate.
  - Roy Battles, 1958-1960 (Box 15, Folder 36 (a, b))
    Correspondence, memos, addresss, introductory, summary, pamphlet. Includes Roy Battles, National Grange.
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, report, draft report, abstract and summary, analysis. Includes Gerald W. Collins, Chamber of Commerce.
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, orders, notices.
  - Clippings, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Department of Transportation, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, memos, statement.
  - John P. Doyle, 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, note. Includes United States Senate.
  - Dual Rates, 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, newsletter, news clipping.
  - Eastern Traffic Bureau, Inc., 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, memo, bulletins, record, news clippings.
  - Lloyd Fagerland, 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, docket proposal, brief, report, petition. Includes James L. Pease, Flathead County Pomona Grange (Montana), United States Department of Agriculture.
  - Featherbedding, 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, Bill, address, pamphlets, newletter, notes on railroad transportation. Includes Daniel P. Loomis, Association of American Railroads.
  - Federal Highway Program, 1959, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Memo, statement, pamphlet.
  - Federal Maritime Board, 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Dockets, correspondence, news clipping.
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, notes, memo, statements, release, agenda, pamphlet. Includes Earl W. Kintner.
  - Florida Fruit and Vegetable Association, 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, article, pamphlets. Includes James T. Duncan.
  - Food Transportation Group, 1959-1966 (Box 16, Folder 14 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, memos, statements, address, sketches, notes, questions, periodical. Includes Eletheer Besley, Mal Xavier, Leonard K. Lobred, International Apple Association, Inc., National Canners Association, National Fisheries Institute.
  - Frozen Food Transportation, 1958, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 15 (a, b))
    Correspondence, statement, questions, bulletin, brief. Includes Lee J. Quassey, National Live Stock Producers Association.
  - Hay, 1957, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, notes. Correpondence includes Sherman Hart.
  - Hardwood Labeling Act, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 17 (a, b))
    Correspondence, testimony, bills. Includes Warren G. Magnuson, E. Howard Gatewood, Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Fine Hardwoods Association.
  - Highway Information Group, 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 18 (a, b))
    Correspondence, memos, communications, talk, news clippings, bulletins. Includes Pyke Johnson.
  - Highways, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Correspondence, memo, statement, Bill, notes. Includes Herschel Newsom.
  - Illegal for-hire trucking, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, programs, remarks, statements. Includes Harold F. Hammond, L. James Harmanson, Jr., Transportation Association of America, National Council of Farmer Cooperatives.
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1951-1961 (Box 16, Folder 21 (a-f))
    Correspondence, dockets, petition, statement. Includes Harold D. McCoy, Jerome K. Lyle.
  - Legislation, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, statement, news release, Bills, resolution. Includes Oren Harris, Warren G. Magnuson, Congress of the United States, United States Senate.
  - National Association of Frozen Food Packers, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    Correspondence, petition, memo, charts. Correpondence includes E. J. Webster, Jr.
  - May 17th Meeting National Council [of Farmer Cooperatives], 1957, 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 24 (a-g))
    Correspondence, statements, finance docket, newsletters, news clippings, pamphlet. Includes L. James Harmanson, Jr., National Council of Farmer Cooperatives.
  - National Council of Farmer Cooperatives, 1957-1960 (Box 16, Folder 25 (a-f))
    Correspondence, agenda, proposal, statement, remarks. Includes L. James Harmanson, Jr.
  - National Fisheries Institute, Inc., 1959 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    Resolution, bulletin.
  - National Grange Annual Session, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 27 (a, b))
    Memos, correspondence, program, notes, pamphlets.
  - National Grange: Deputy News Letters, 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - National Grange Executive Committee Meetings, 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    News clipping, newsletter, digests, minutes.
  - National Grange Executive Committee Meeting, Apr. 1960 (Box 16, Folder 30 (a, b))
    Correspondence, notes, Bill, news clipping, periodical, statements.
  - National Grange: Committee on Grange Law and Good of the Order (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - National Grange: "The Grange Surveys America's Transportation Situation", 1952 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - National Grange: The Green Letter, 1960, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    Newsletters and enclosures.
  - National Grange: National Transportation Policy - Report of National Grange Transportation Committee, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - National Grange: Herschel D. Newsom, Master, 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    Memos, correspondence, address, statement, biography.
  - National Grange Position on Transportation Issues, 1956, 1959, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    Notes, correspondence, memos, report, news clipping.
  - National Grange: "Reports to Executive Committee and Miscellaneous Papers", 1959 (Box 16, Folder 37 (a, b))
    Notes, correspondence, check list, news clippings, memo, statements.
  - National Grange: Statements, 1956, 1958-1961 (Box 16, Folder 38 (a-d))
  - National Grange: Transportation Sessions Committee of the 1959 National Grange Convention, 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 1 (a-k))
    Correspondence, notes, subject lists, reports, pamphlets (mostly exhibit items.)
  - National Highway Users Conference, Inc., 1954-1959 (Box 17, Folder 2 (a, b))
    Correspondence, compilation, reports, newsletters, vehicle code book, recommendations.
  - National Highway Users Conference: Agenda, Joint Meeting Board of Governors and Administrate Committee, Sept. 24, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Agenda (notebook), memo, notes, newsletters.
  - National Highway Users Conference, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 4 (a, b))
    Correspondence, reports, news releases, pamphlets, summary of minutes, charts, carbon memos. Includes Yule Fisher.
  - National Highway Users Conference, Dec. 1961 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, supplement, memos, agenda, summary. Includes Arthur C. Butler.
  - National Highway Users Conference, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 6 (a-f))
    Correspondence, memos, newsletters, summaries of minutes, notations.
  - National Highway Users Conference: National Capital Transportation Agency, 1961, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    News releases (presidents' messages), critiques.
  - National Highway Users Conference, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 8 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, newsletters, reports, pamphlets, memo.
  - National Highway Users Conference, Inc. Meeting, June 27, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Reports, newsletter.
  - National Highway Users Conference: Agenda, Joint Meeting-Board of Governors and Administrative Committee, Sept. 13, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Agenda (notebook), minutes, correspondence, memos, draft.
  - National Highway Users Conference, Oct. 18, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Guidelines, correspondence, agenda, notes.
  - National Highway Users Conference, Dec. 14, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 12 (a, b))
    Memos, analysis, agenda, pamphlets. Includes Arthur C. Butler.
  - National Highway Users Conference: "The Highway User", 1962, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    Periodicals.
  - National Highway Users Conference, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, agenda, resolution, study recommendations, analysis, views, newsletter, reports, notations.
  - Parcel Post: I.C.C. Docket No. 32158, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 15 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, exceptions.
  - "S. 1306 - Parcel Post", 1957, 1959, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, memo, press release, statement, pamphlet. Includes William B. Henderson, Parcel Post Association.
  - Passenger Train Service Act of 1960, 1959, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, Bills, news clipping, statistics.
  - Potomac Grange Study Committee on the Exercise of the Powers of Eminent Domain, 1952-1959 (Box 17, Folder 18 (a-d))
    Correspondence, minutes, reports, pamphlets.
  - Private Carrier Conference, Inc., 1959, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 19 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, bulletins, pamphlets. Includes Vincent L. O'Donnell, Caughey B. Culpepper, Atlanta Freight Bureau.
  - Private Truck Council of America, Inc., 1958-1960 (Box 17, Folder 20 (a, b))
    Correspondence, notes, reports, bulletins, pamphlets. Includes James D. Mann.
  - Produce Packaging Association, 1959, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 21 (a, b, c))
    Bulletins, yearbook.
  - Public Law-85-626, 1959, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 1 (a-h))
    Correspondence, memo, news clippings, Bill, statements, testimonies, lists. Includes George E. Vawter, True D. Morse, Sun-Maid Raisin Growers of California, United States Department of Agriculture.
  - Lee J. Quasey, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, biographical sketch, announcement.
  - Railroads: re Cabinet Committee Transportation Policy Report, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, memo. Includes Jervis Langdon, Jr., Association of Southeastern Railroads.
  - Railroads: Car supply, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Release, statements.
  - Railroad Depreciation, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, proposal. Includes J. Don Parel, Association of American Railroads.
  - Railroads: Legislation, 1952-1960 (Box 18, Folder 6 (a-e))
    Correspondence, statements, Bills, news clippings, pamphlets. Includes Warren G. Magnuson, George Smathers, United States Senate (Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce).
  - Railroads: Retirement and Unemployment Insurance, 1954, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 7 (a-d))
    Correspondence, notes, statements, report, Act, pamphlet. Includes Dwight D. Eisenhower, J. Carter Fort, Association of American Railroads.
  - St. Lawrence Seaway, 1957-1959 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, tearsheet, memo, pamphlet.
  - Transportation Association, 1958, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 9 (a, b))
    Correspondence, newsletters, annual report. Includes Harold F. Hammond.
  - Transportation Association of America - Japanese Transportation Study Team, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, memo, notes, questionnaire, address, summation, pamphlets.
  - Statements re Transport Diversification Bills, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 11 (a-e))
  - Transportation Policy - Comments on Cabinet Committee Transportation Policy Report, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    Comments, dictabelt record.
  - Transportation Policy - Comments on H.R. 6141, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, appendix. Includes J. M. Johnson, Interstate Commerce Commission.
  - Transportation Policy - Views of Other Organizations, 1955, 1956, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 14 (a-g))
    Correspondence, articles, resolutions, pamphlets, statements.
  - Trip-leasing, 1951-1956 (Box 18, Folder 15 (a-h))
    Correspondence, article, memos, petition, notes, testimony, statement, Bill, newsletter, analysis, news clipping, pamphlet, tearsheet.
  - Truck Reparations, 1959, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, Bill, note, memo. Includes Lester J. Dorr, National Industrial Traffic League.
  - United States Department of Agriculture, 1938, 1956-1961 (Box 18, Folder 17 (a-e))
    Summary, petition, pamphlets (annotated), correspondence, docket, addresses, report, maps, charts, memo. Includes J. L. Pease, United States Department of Agriculture.
  - United States Department of Commerce, 1960, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    News releases, statement.
  - United States Tariff Commission, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    Notices, proclamation.
  - George E. Vawter, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    Includes Sun-Maid Raisin Growers of California.
  - Waterways, 1953, 1954, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 21 (a, b))
    Draft, correspondence, annotated testimony, petition, memo.
  - Dewey C. Wayne, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    Includes North Carolina Department of Agriculture.
  - Western Railways, 1959-1961 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    Correspondence, newsletters, news release. Includes J. Blaine Quinn, California State Grange.
  - Wool, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Correspondence, submittal, rate chart.
- Series VIII. Economist - Lloyd C. Halverson
  - "Commodity Dollar", 1944-1955 (Box 19, Folder 1 (a, b))
    Correspondence, address, reprint, pamphlet. Includes Benjamin Graham, Frank D. Graham, Albert G. Hart, Committee for Economic Stability, Princeton University.
  - Council on Economic Advisors and Joint Committee, 1944-1948 (Box 19, Folder 2 (a-d))
    Correspondence, indexes, memos, reprints, statement, article, testimonies, news clipping. Includes Edwin G. Nourse, Gunther Stein, Executive Office of the President (U.S.), Council of Economic Advisors.
  - Economic Planning - Miscellaneous, 1944-1946 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Address, memo, correspondence, article, reprint, pamphlets.
  - Economic Policy - Transportation, 1945, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, reports.
  - FCA Miscellaneous, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Remarks, memos, tables, notes.
  - Farm Credit Act, 1945-1953 (Box 19, Folder 7 (a, b))
    Statements, testimony, analysis, address, correspondence, Bill, pamphlet. Includes Sam H. Bober, National Farm Loan Associations, Advisory Committee.
  - Farm Credit Bill, 1952, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 8 (a-d))
    Correspondence, memo, analysis, statement, testimony, proceedings. Includes T. Hervey Hedgepeth, William D. Kaley, Hedgepeth and Norsworthy, Federation of National Farm Loan Associations of the United States.
  - Farm Credit Legislation, 1951-1953 (Box 19, Folder 9 (a-e))
    Correspondence, statements, comments, memos, telegram, photo, pamphlets, Bills, notes, minutes. Includes Harvey Hedgepeth, J. D. Anderson, R. W. Mize, Hedgepeth and Norsworthy, Production Credit Association.
  - Finance, 1950, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, pamphlets.
  - Hedgepeth Letters, 1951, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 11 (a, b, c))
  - Joint Farm Credit Committee, 1948-1952 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, minutes. Includes Gwynn Garnett, John H. Davis, American Farm Bureau Federation, National Council of Farmer Cooperatives.
  - Low Income Farmers, 1950, 1953-1956 (Box 19, Folder 13 (a-e))
    Study, release, reports, note, outline, editorial, clipping, pamphlets, correspondence, memos. Includes Don F. Pielstick, National Council of the Churches of Christ - Division of Home Missions.
  - Low Income People Problem, 1949-1955 (Box 19, Folder 14 (a, b))
    Memo, correspondence, reference list, reports.
  - Monetary Banking and Fiscal Policy, 1948-1953 (Box 19, Folder 15 (a-f))
    Correspondence, memos, newsletter, statement, address, charts. Includes Theodore W. Schultz, Thomas Roy Jones, A. W. Rees, Alden A. Potter, Lorenzo U. Bergeron, Department of Economics, University of Chicago, American Type Founders, Inc., Western Institute of Economic Research.
  - Money and Banking, 1943-1953 (Box 19, Folder 16 (a-e))
    Address, report, correspondence, articles, pamphlets, treatise, report. Includes L. Sumner Pruyne, The First National Bank of Boston.
  - Money and Banking Committee, 1899, 1946-1955 (Box 19, Folder 17 (a, b, c))
    News clipping, pamphlets, reports, resolutions.
  - National Planning Association, 1954-1956 (Box 19, Folder 18 (a-d))
    List, memo, correspondence, review. Includes John Miller, Harry B. Caldwell, Iowa State Grange.
  - National Planning Association Booklets, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 19 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, minutes, research paper, review draft, statement, analysis.
  - NPA Advisory Committee, 1956, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, statement.
  - Other Farm Credit Correspondence, 1951, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 21 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, minutes, agenda, notes, summary. Includes R. W. Mize, C. W. Patterson, Sam H. Bober, C. H. Matthews, Production Credit Associations, Federation of National Farm Loan Associations, National Farm Loan Associations, Advisory Committee.
  - Parcel Post Association, 1956, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Bills, pamphlet, reply, analysis.
  - Schools ("Better Schools"), 1956, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    Newspapers, newsletter.
  - Spray Residue, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    Notes, bulletin, report.
  - Social Security, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, fact sheets, notice, pamphlets.
  - State Department, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    Correspondence, memo. Includes R. G. Brierley, Archer-Daniels-Midland Company.
  - State Grange Meetings, 1946, 1947, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    Lists, correspondence, roster, address. Includes Wib Justi.
  - State Masters, 1947-1954 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    Correspondence, memo, talk. Includes Herschel D. Newsom, Franklin C. Nixon, Harry B. Caldwell, Indiana State Grange, New Jersey State Grange, North Carolina State Grange.
  - Statements, 1949, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Statistics - General, 1951, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Correspondence, questions, statistics.
  - Subsidy Program, 1945, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    Correspondence, tear sheet, news clipping.
  - Tax Paper - Grange, Mar. 1945, 1944, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    Correspondence, drafts, paper, notes. Includes James G. Maddox, Bureau of Agricultural Economics, United States Department of Agriculture.
  - Tax Paper - Atlantic City Postwar Conference June 14, 1946, 1945, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 1 (a-f))
    Correspondence, papers, statements, agendas. Includes Vada Horsch, National Postwar Conference.
  - Technical Assistance Program 1955, 1956, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, list, newsletter.
  - Telephones, 1945-1949 (Box 20, Folder 3 (a-e))
    Correspondence, draft, notes, news clipping, pamphlets, Bills, facts, statistics, reports. Includes Clyde S. Bailey, V. A. Droser, United States Independent Telephone Association, American Telephone and Telegraph Company.
  - Treasury Reports, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, agenda, charts, drafts, memo. Includes Vernon L. Clark, United States Savings Bonds Division, Treasury Department.
  - Under-employed Farmers, 1951, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Article, news clipping, release, pamphlets.
  - United States Department of Agriculture, 1945-1956 (Box 20, Folder 6 (a, b, c))
    Tables, memo, newsletter, summary, article, typescript, correspondence, news clipping. Includes Joseph Wheeler, Office of Budget and Finance, United States Department of Agriculture.
  - U.S. Savings Bonds, 1948-1952 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, minutes, draft of statement. Includes William I. Myers, National Agricultural Savings Bonds Committee.
  - Universal Training, 1945, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Statements, analysis, minutes.
  - Valley Authorities, 1944, 1951, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 9 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, memo, address, notes, article, statement, pamphlets. Includes C. F. Clayton, David E. Lilienthal, Tennessee Valley Agricultural Correlating Committee, Tennessee Valley Authority.
  - "Veterans", 1944 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Testimonies, memo, pamphlets.
  - War Business, 1943, 1950, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 11 (a, b))
    Statements, remark, pamphlets, memos, correspondence.
  - Water Law - pamphlet, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Water Pollution - correspondence, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Watersheds - statement, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Weed laws - pamphlet, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Wheat Agreement, 1947-1953 (Box 20, Folder 16 (a-d))
    Text, draft, agreement, address, statement, pamphlet, memos. Includes J. T. Sanders.
  - White House Conference on Education, 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, summary, workbook, pamphlets.
  - World Alliance News Letter (Church Peace Union, Publ.), 1957 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Series IX. Public Relations Director, C. W. ("Jack") Jackson
  - "Ag Census", 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    Facts, questionnaires, articles, memo, statement, photocopy, map, correspondence.
  - Agricultural Editors, 1957-1961 (Box 20, Folder 20 (a-j))
    Correspondence, article, questions and answers, notes, reports, membership list. Includes Dick Hanson, Frank Waddle, Marvin Russell, Successful Farming, Better Farming Methods, The Nebraska Farmer.
  - Ag-Statistics General, 1954, 1957, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    Note, correspondence, articles, maps.
  - Annual Report of Grange Achievements - memos, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Annual Sessions Ideas, 1958, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    Correspondence, news releases, pamphlets, memo.
  - Annual Session - 1956 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    Correspondence, lists.
  - Annual Session - 1957 (Box 20, Folder 25 (a-i))
    Correspondence, memos, lists, reports, address, guidebook, news release, proof, notebook, programs, certificates.
  - Annual Session - 1958, 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 26 (a-g))
    Memos, correspondence, addresses, news releases, lists.
  - Pre-convention Material - 1959 (Box 20, Folder 27 (a, b))
    Correspondence, memos, news releases, statements, news clipping.
  - Annual Session - 1959, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 28 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, memos, magazine, facts, questionnaires, articles.
  - Annual Session - 1959, Material Produced at Convention (Box 20, Folder 29)
    Memos, articles, lists.
  - Annual Session 1959 - Material released at session (Box 20, Folder 30)
    Bulletins, news releases, address, memo, summary.
  - Roy Battles, 1957-1960 (Box 21, Folder 1 (a-e))
    Memos, summary, address, correspondence, biography, news release, draft.
  - Charles Bowling, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Appendix, memos, biography, correspondence.
  - "Publicity on Cibolo Grange...", 1957 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Community Service Contest 1955, 1953, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Radio scripts, information, news releases.
  - Community Service Contest - 1956 Material, 1948-1952, 1954-1956 (Box 21, Folder 5 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, news releases, statistics, pamphlets. Includes Edward F. Holter, National Grange Community Service Contest Committee.
  - Community Service Contest - 1957 Finalists (Box 21, Folder 6 (a, b))
    Memo, list, background reports, notes.
  - Community Service Contest - 1957 Judging Tour, Press Kit (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Community Service Contest - 1957 Releases and Correspondence. (Box 21, Folder 8 (a-e))
    Correspondence, releases, lists, tabulation, photo. Includes William Whitsitt, Public Relations, Sears, Roebuck and Co.
  - Community Service Contest - 1957 Judging Tour (Box 21, Folder 9 (a, b))
    Correspondence, memo, summaries, itinerary, tabulation.
  - Community Service Contest 1958, Jackson's personal tour notes (Box 21, Folder 10 (a, b))
    Notes, remarks, correspondence, news clipping.